{
    "BookName": "Analyst Toeic",
    "Units": [
        {
            "Unit": 1,
            "Part2": {
                "Src": "assets/data/4.Analyst_Toeic/06.mp3",
                "Quiz": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Whom did you get that message from?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "The manager of the payroll department.",
                            "Yesterday, we talked about it.",
                            "John didn't know about the message."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "The manager of the payroll department."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Whose jacket is that?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "It was made in China.",
                            "It's made of cotton.",
                            "It's mine."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "It's mine."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Who didn't attend the meeting yesterday?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "John forgot about the meeting.",
                            "It finished late.",
                            "The personnel manager."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "The personnel manager."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "Unit": 2,
            "Part2": {
                "Src": "assets/data/4.Analyst_Toeic/07.mp3",
                "Quiz": [
                    {
                        "Question": "When did you get up this morning?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "At dawn.",
                            "Yes, I got up early this morning.",
                            "Because of a loud noise."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "At dawn."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "When do you think you can finish the report?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "I didn't think it was difficult.",
                            "It will be done by the third.",
                            "I'm looking forward to it."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "It will be done by the third."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "When are you visiting the Hong Kong branch?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "I'm going in a few days.",
                            "Yes, I am visiting it soon.",
                            "I didn't go to Hong Kong this time."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "I'm going in a few days."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "Unit": 3,
            "Part2": {
                "Src": "assets/data/4.Analyst_Toeic/08.mp3",
                "Quiz": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Where is a shoe store near here?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "Leather shoes last longer.",
                            "The shop has a large selection of shoes.",
                            "Down the street, past the church."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "Down the street, past the church."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Where's your new office?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "I'm in the cafeteria.",
                            "On the fourth floor.",
                            "It's too big."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "On the fourth floor."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Where do you usually buy your coffee?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "It's rather expensive these days.",
                            "At a little store next to the supermarket.",
                            "I don't drink coffee at work."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "At a little store next to the supermarket."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "Unit": 4,
            "Part2": {
                "Src": "assets/data/4.Analyst_Toeic/09.mp3",
                "Quiz": [
                    {
                        "Question": "What time does the movie start?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "It will last about two hours.",
                            "There is no theater here.",
                            "I don't know. Let's look at the timetable."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "I don't know. Let's look at the timetable."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "What does your sister do?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "He works at a bank.",
                            "She's a salesperson.",
                            "She can help you any time you want."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "She's a salesperson."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "What are you going to tell Mr. Runfeld when he calls?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "He is going to call this afternoon.",
                            "I'll think of something to say, so don't worry.",
                            "I couldn't answer the phone."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "I'll think of something to say, so don't worry."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "Unit": 5,
            "Part2": {
                "Src": "assets/data/4.Analyst_Toeic/10.mp3",
                "Quiz": [
                    {
                        "Question": "How would you like your coffee?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "No sugar, please.",
                            "Yes, I would like coffee.",
                            "I prefer coffee to tea."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "No sugar, please."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "How long have you been here?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "About three and a half years.",
                            "It took three hours by bus.",
                            "I'm fine. How about you?"
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "About three and a half years."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "How long does it take to get to the town center from here?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "There's a bus every thirty minutes.",
                            "No more than 20 minutes, if the traffic is light.",
                            "I'm driving to the town center tonight."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "No more than 20 minutes, if the traffic is light."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "Unit": 6,
            "Part2": {
                "Src": "assets/data/4.Analyst_Toeic/11.mp3",
                "Quiz": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Why do you think he didn't support our plan?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "I don't think so at all.",
                            "He seems to dislike any new ideas.",
                            "You're right about that."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "He seems to dislike any new ideas."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Why was he late for school?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "It's not my fault.",
                            "I think he took the wrong bus.",
                            "School finished at 5:00."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "I think he took the wrong bus."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Why didn't you tell me that he had resigned?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "I thought that you already knew.",
                            "Yes, he resigned yesterday.",
                            "Because it's a hot day."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, he resigned yesterday."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "Unit": 7,
            "Part2": {
                "Src": "assets/data/4.Analyst_Toeic/12.mp3",
                "Quiz": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Didn't you go to the book fair?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "Sure, if you want to.",
                            "I did, but I didn't stay long.",
                            "Yes, I didn't."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "I did, but I didn't stay long."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Are you going to attend the conference?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "I guess so.",
                            "We were too late.",
                            "From the 2nd to the 5th."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "From the 2nd to the 5th."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Could you show me how this fax machine works?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "It is a new fax machine.",
                            "Of course. It's very simple.",
                            "Has the fax already been sent?"
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "Of course. It's very simple."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "Unit": 8,
            "Part2": {
                "Src": "assets/data/4.Analyst_Toeic/13.mp3",
                "Quiz": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Are you going to buy a new computer or just continue using the old one?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "Neither. I'm going to lease one.",
                            "Yes, I'd like one, thank you.",
                            "That's impossible. I can't afford a new one."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "Neither. I'm going to lease one."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Which do you prefer, the yellow T-shirt or the blue one?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "Yes, I like the blue one.",
                            "Neither.",
                            "Both of them are very cheap."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, I like the blue one."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Is Joseph or Manuel going to present the proposal?",
                        "Answers": [
                            "Yes, they are going to make the presentation.",
                            "Manuel said he would do it.",
                            "Well, I'd like to, but I'm busy."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, they are going to make the presentation."
                    }
                ]
            }
        },
        {
            "Unit": 9,
            "Part2": {
                "Src": "assets/data/4.Analyst_Toeic/14.mp3",
                "Quiz": [
                    {
                        "Question": "I've put the accounting files on your desk.",
                        "Answers": [
                            "Thanks. I'll look at them later.",
                            "I haven't phoned yet.",
                            "It's going to be difficult to finish."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "Thanks. I'll look at them later."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "Thank you for taking the time to come here in person.",
                        "Answers": [
                            "There are many people in this branch.",
                            "Don't mention it. It's my pleasure.",
                            "What do you feel like eating?"
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "Don't mention it. It's my pleasure."
                    },
                    {
                        "Question": "I've arranged the meeting for three o'clock on Thursday.",
                        "Answers": [
                            "I don't enjoy meetings.",
                            "I have had a lot of phone calls today.",
                            "Good, I'll mark it on my planner."
                        ],
                        "CorrectAnswer": "Good, I'll mark it on my planner."
                    }
                ]
            }
        }
    ],
    "Test": {
        "Src2": "assets/data/4.Analyst_Toeic/15.mp3",
        "Quiz": [
            {
                "Question": "How long has he been gone?",
                "Answers": [
                    "Until tomorrow.",
                    "For half an hour.",
                    "Next week."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "For half an hour."
            },
            {
                "Question": "I'm afraid I can't hear you.",
                "Answers": [
                    "I'm sorry. I'll speak louder.",
                    "Yes, I can come up now.",
                    "I really can't say."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "I'm sorry. I'll speak louder."
            },
            {
                "Question": "Would you like to go now?",
                "Answers": [
                    "In a few minutes.",
                    "I go there every day.",
                    "I usually go by taxi."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "In a few minutes."
            },
            {
                "Question": "How often do they update the computers?",
                "Answers": [
                    "Yes, they often do.",
                    "Two or three times a year.",
                    "About one or two weeks."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "Two or three times a year."
            },
            {
                "Question": "Why did you turn the air conditioner on?",
                "Answers": [
                    "It isn't working very well.",
                    "It's in good condition.",
                    "It's a little warm in here."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "It's a little warm in here."
            },
            {
                "Question": "Didn't you used to work at Macy's with Sarah Davis?",
                "Answers": [
                    "When do we begin work?",
                    "Yes, that's right.",
                    "I certainly do."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, that's right."
            },
            {
                "Question": "Who is responsible for this?",
                "Answers": [
                    "I don't have it.",
                    "I believe Susan is.",
                    "No, I'm not."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "I believe Susan is."
            },
            {
                "Question": "I have a bit of a cold.",
                "Answers": [
                    "It's nearly spring.",
                    "You should take it easy.",
                    "That's a wonderful idea."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "You should take it easy."
            },
            {
                "Question": "Whose briefcase is this?",
                "Answers": [
                    "It's my boss's.",
                    "They're probably lost.",
                    "His luggage is full."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "It's my boss's."
            },
            {
                "Question": "Would you like tea or coffee?",
                "Answers": [
                    "It's fine, thanks.",
                    "Yes, please.",
                    "Coffee would be nice."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "Coffee would be nice."
            },
            {
                "Question": "How many stories tall is that building?",
                "Answers": [
                    "About thirty-five.",
                    "I read it already.",
                    "Yes, it's quite high."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "About thirty-five."
            },
            {
                "Question": "Did he fill out the form completely?",
                "Answers": [
                    "He forgot to sign and date it.",
                    "Once in a while it loses its shape.",
                    "Could I borrow your pen?"
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "He forgot to sign and date it."
            },
            {
                "Question": "If you don't answer the letter, who will?",
                "Answers": [
                    "My assistant will.",
                    "Because I don't want to.",
                    "The answer is wrong."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "My assistant will."
            },
            {
                "Question": "When does the sale finish?",
                "Answers": [
                    "Yes, it has finished.",
                    "Office equipment is on sale.",
                    "It runs until next Friday."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "It runs until next Friday."
            },
            {
                "Question": "Could you open these desk drawers for me?",
                "Answers": [
                    "I can't. They're stuck.",
                    "Sure, you can close them.",
                    "It opens at four o'clock."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "I can't. They're stuck."
            },
            {
                "Question": "When does your subscription expire?",
                "Answers": [
                    "In March.",
                    "For one year.",
                    "Twice a week."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "In March."
            },
            {
                "Question": "When do you want to discuss my memo?",
                "Answers": [
                    "No, but I'll finish it by tomorrow.",
                    "I need to write several more pages.",
                    "How about this afternoon?"
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "How about this afternoon?"
            },
            {
                "Question": "Where is Brian Ivan's desk?",
                "Answers": [
                    "It's at seven-fifty.",
                    "It's over there, by the window.",
                    "Certainly, just a moment."
                ],
                "CorrectAnswer": "It's over there, by the window."
            }
        ]
    }
}